https://heartofstonestudio.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Glossary of termsCart
Home » Privacy Policy
COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY
This site is owned and operated by Heart of Stone Studio. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Heart of Stone Studio, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.
Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.
Heart of Stone Studio gathers two types of information about users:
1) Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys:
2) Like many other online businesses, we gather aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does Heart of Stone Studio divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.
Heart of Stone Studio Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:
1. Electronic newsletters policy (Dispatches)
Heart of Stone Studio offers a free electronic newsletter to users. We gather the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.
2. “E-mail this to a friend” policy
Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking “e-mail this to a friend”. The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.
3. Usage tracking
Heart of Stone Studio tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. Heart of Stone Studio does break down overall usage statistics according to a user’s domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser).
Heart of Stone Studio sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.
4. Cookies
We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Heart of Stone Studio uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.
5. Child Protection
Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly collect, either online or offline, personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. Children under 18 may use the site only with the permission of a parent or guardian.
Products of Interest
No products were found matching your selection.
Magical Navigator
To open a category you want to explore, click on the arrow to its right.
Then pick a subcategory or theme and click on its right arrow to see all the stone species that express that theme. Click on any stone to visit its page.
Product categoriesCabochons
Captivating Patterns
Abstract Art
Bumblebee Jasper
Cherry Creek Jasper
Carasite
Chinese Writing Stone
Laguna Lace Agate
Chesterfield Jasper (Polychrome Jasper)
Norwegian Moonstone (Larvikite)
Citron Magnesite (Lemon Chrysoprase)
